We're now going to create the next
API request,
which is the decision.
So that was,
is going to be called the post-decision,
and that is where when the manager clicks on the approved button,
we need to write that information into the data table in Workato.
So we're going to create that recipe
and remember that data will be.
Updating this data table.
So let's go ahead and create that.
We're going to create a recipe.
And it's gonna be called the post decision.
And we're gonna build an API endpoint
and we're gonna start building.
Now,
unlike the previous
example,
we are getting
parameters in the request.
And so,
we need to
identify what the schema is.
So,
we'll click on use JSON.
And here we're going to get 3 items coming in in the request.
And it'll be the record ID,
the decision,
which is going to be approved,
uh,
or reject,
and then the approver email.
And we'll generate the schema.
So,
this is a big difference now
because we need to tell Rorcado
additional data is coming in and you'll need to do something with that.
And now,
just like we did before,
we need to configure the response for this API so we'll call this success.
Uh,
it's a standard response
and 200 OK.
And once again,
we'll need to add the JSON.
What are we going to send back the information?
What would it,
what the schema look like?
OK.
We'll have the record ID and the status.
And generate the schema.
OK,
so now we know that the recipe,
it's telling us
what to expect,
what are we gonna get,
and what
the output's going to look like.
Now,
we're gonna click on add step,
action in app.
Now,
what are we doing?
We're going to be updating the table in Workado.
So,
the Workado data table is going to be
updated with the decision.
Unlike the previous one where we used an array,
this is a flat file.
We're just gonna update a single record.
So,
update record is the correct item here.
We need to make sure we select the right table so computer request approval.
And we're going to uh use the record ID.
And
now we see here on the left,
we have the decision and the approval email.
We need to
map that.
So,
we get those now listed here.
So we have the rover email.
And the most important one is the decision.
Approve,
reject.
OK,
so we need to map the information that is coming in.
Through this API,
we need to map it to what are the.
Places in the data table stored by Worado,
so that it knows where to
update the record.
OK,
and then the last piece.
We're going to do is
actually action an app and then API platform by Worcado.
So we're going to respond
and it was a success,
and we only just used one and then we'll go ahead and uh
Apply.
To show all of these,
OK?
And we're going to show the record ID and the status.
We're going to send that back in the response body
back to the app on the iPhone.
And now we will save,
we have completed everything in this API.
So,
the first one's going to take the request,
and remember,
this is,
Getting a single record,
it's not an
array.
It's gonna get the information for which record to change.
We've mapped.
In the
Uh,
recipe here.
We're in the data table,
we're going to make the changes,
and then what are we gonna return back to in this API back to the app.
So we've clicked on save.
I'm going to exit
the editing.
And then I'm going to go back to,
Our project
and we see here now we have the post decision.
So,
we have the data table,
we have the pending request that gives us all the items that are pending,
and this is when the
manager clicks on the button approve.
This is the API that will be called.